{
    "id": "f8a02d81db064de98e631062e261aa6f",
    "title": "Possessives And Reflexives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is ................................ bag.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He injured ................................ while playing football.",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, the reflexive is used.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "himself",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She cooked dinner ......................................",
            "description": "The emphatic is used to emphasize an idea. ",
            "answers": [
                "herself",
                "hers",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He snatched the paper from ........................................ hand.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't believe ..................................... story.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "yourself",
                "yours",
                "your"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw it with ....................................... own eyes.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There was no one to help me so I had to do it .......................................",
            "description": "The emphatic pronoun is used to emphasize.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Someone broke into .......................................... house while we were away.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "us",
                "ourselves",
                "our"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Please do it ......................................",
            "description": "The emphatic pronoun is used to emphasize.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think it is ....................................... responsibility.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Be careful or you will injure ........................................",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, the reflexive is used.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "you itself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your fault, not ...........................................",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}